It's a bit heavy
, it's all down there, it's all my God,
if you don't wear a suit
, just like in China, the dean will catch you and make you stand,
so here I am,
I'm going to give you a little test.
This is the trash I picked up yesterday,
coucou les amis (French) : Hello friends)
Hello, all the cuties of Shitu,
I am your Yooupi
and welcome to my channel.
Today is
the day you picked up the trash that you have been urging me to do for a long time. The last time I picked up the trash, I told you that
I would start a new series.
Isn’t this what happened
when we took the picked up rubbish and
made it in various Chinese homes in Europe
? Today our first protagonist
is studying in the world’s number one
hotel management school
, and he is the school’s cooking competition champion
and has won awards in many hotels. I have interned at a Michelin three-star restaurant
, so let’s not talk nonsense.
Let’s take a look at
what kind of ingredients we can pick up today.
Now I came to the back of a fruit and vegetable store.
There are a lot of trash cans here
. No matter what they are, as long as they are edible.
You can feel it when you touch it.
It's all garbage.
This is baking paper.
Because there is a bakery next to it
. It's all baking paper.
There is no bread.
There are some leftovers in the corner,
but it's unnecessary. I definitely can't eat it.
There are some corns here
.
I threw them in the store.
I opened them to see if I can eat
them. They are still good.
They are a little bit thick
but they are still edible.
I harvested three corns.
This is cheese
, but this one has been opened
and it is full of cheese and cannot be eaten.
Here is an avocado,
this is all cheese,
the cheese is broken,
and it is thrown out from the store.
There is also an avocado
, but this avocado is hard when you pinch it.
You see, these are all thrown out from the supermarket.
This is blood sausage.
Harvest two avocados.
It's okay. Anyway
, there is no crack.
There is also a piece of garbage from their bakery here.
You see, it is all bread
. This is the flour they did not use up.
When they closed the store, they would knead it into a lump
and bake it like this.
Many farmers came to pick it up like this. The flour lumps
are fed to their chickens, ducks
, horses, sheep, etc.
This box contains degradable things
, but people can't eat it and throw it outside.
There are some radishes
in Yanba, Yanba, and
my first protagonist must give them to him. It’s a bit more difficult
to make this kind of braised vegetables with Michelin effect.
I think avocados are easy to pick up
and they
are so expensive in supermarkets
. There is also an egg shell
with
4 eggs in it. These 2
are good.
The two good ones are broken.
You see, this egg does not expire until June 9th.
I think why it is reduced in price
or thrown away now
is probably because it is damaged.
Let’s take a look at
the melon
honeydew melon.
It seems to be a bit broken and
moldy,
but When the skin is dry,
I need to fold the box down
so that it is more convenient.
This one is also a bit broken.
This one is not as good as the one just now.
Let's see if there are any others.
There is one
with red pepper.
It looks good.
That one is in honeydew
photography. The teacher picked up
the fed food.
This one is in
good condition.
It’s too wasteful.
It’s completely good.
This is the salad dish thrown out from the store.
God, this salad dish is still fresh and fresh.
There is also watermelon.
Watermelon must not be eaten.
It is not sealed.
This lettuce
is fresh and this melon
is not in very good condition.
I went straight to check out
the other good one and made it for my friend to see.
It’s absolutely good.
It’s very good.
I love it
in France during the summer. If you hit
a melon with some ham or something like this
and sell it in a supermarket,
no one will buy it.
Now many supermarkets have begun to make some improvements,
such as donating it to some charitable organizations
or giving it to some charity kitchens.
Just use this. Grow food
and give it to others for free.
Okay,
let's take these to the next one
. Now I'm at the back of a bakery.
Everyone who watched my video should know that
bakeries are easier to pick up
than other stores.
Look at this shape.
Someone with experience like me would n’t
lose food like this.
Is this a baguette? It’s
not
all a paper bag.
I thought it was a baguette.
These are all baking paper.
Logically speaking, the store that just closed this weekend
should have something
. None of them are empty.
I feel the
soft
bag. Is
this bag made of paper?
This bag seems to
have been brought out quickly.
These two bags seem to be
my God. They are so heavy. Oh
my God.
There is another bag.
This bag is not. This bag is. This bag of plastic bottles
must be
because I've touched it,
but I'm not sure yet.
I'll try not to touch it.
Take a
look.
Oh my god, it's
all
my hands. I've already handled it. Look, look
, look, and so.
I've been chewing a big piece of bread
these days. These are all sandwiches.
This bread is so soft.
It's completely soft
. I baked it this morning and threw it away.
I'm afraid I'm going to have a big victory today.
I asked how to pinch the bread.
It's the kind of paper that's glue.
It's glue. I thought it was tape,
but it turns out it
’s all bread.
Oh
my god, my God. It
’s
all down there. It’s all my God.
There are also marshmallow donuts.
They’re all donuts.
There’s another one as big as this one.
I don’t know what it is. Oh
my god, the butter tart.
Brother just lost it.
There’s a lot of flour underneath
. It ’s all flour
. I haven’t picked up so many breads for a while.
Although the croissant
is a bit wilted , you
can take it back and bake it.
It
is still edible and
very soft.
I baked the old saying today
without any problem
on the public screen.
My friends who watched my video for the first time may be a little shocked,
but old fans should be used to this kind of scene.
Why are the bakeries so discarded?
This is because bread
cannot be sold overnight in France.
If it is not sold out in one day
, it will be thrown away at night.
What should you do when you see this picture
?
What does it mean?
Why is there no ham in the sandwich
? What
does that mean
? The employee took away all the ham,
leaving only a piece of bread with all the ham gone.
You may think this appearance is a bit exaggerated
, but this situation exists in every bakery.
This is included in their Within the operating cost,
let's take this bread first
, but I may pick
it later. I can't take that much.
Then there is a store next to it.
I went to the store to take another look.
Now I have arrived at the back of a small grocery store.
Its box is right here.
Then we take a look.
The food I threw away at once
, I think it is expired food.
The ham has expired.
It must have started to become watery.
I can't eat
it. What is this?
This is scallops,
shrimp, shrimp and mussel jelly
. It should be
expired.
That's it. It is a product with an expiration date
of November 23 , and this box is
expired in February 24.
This box of 23 years is definitely not good
. I can only check if this box can be used.
What kind of fish are these?
This
should also be expired, right?
It expires on April 2nd.
It's the kind of pickled fish.
Here is the sausage.
I won't take it out. It's totally good. Look,
there's also this kind of fruit basket.
It's pretty good.
I can recycle the waste. I can
take it back and keep it for myself. The house can also be
made entirely of wood and it is very strong.
You see,
here is
the sausage again. This is bread . What is the date of May 24?
I can’t see
the expiration date. I think it’s
okay. I have something else.
This is
a pie crust for baking a tower.
This is fine. I gave it to my friend
and he can use this to make things.
The date is May 14th. What is today,
the 12th?
There are two days before the expiration date.
And the bulge has not been flattened yet.
This box has been flattened.
Flatten it. I don’t want
any other dishes.
What kind of chicken
is this
? There’s also a box of chicken.
I’m not sure if I can eat
it. It looks like it’s in good condition.
I took it to
the supermarket and it seems to be okay.
I picked up some things. Some
of them are in bad condition.
You can see that it is not in good condition and has water inside.
Although it may not have reached the date sometimes
, I still don’t eat it.
I looked here and
there is nothing here.
They are all plastic
bags.
There are some paper boxes on top of the paper bags.
I went up to take a look. Many
friends asked if
no one wanted these boxes or anything
. This kind is for collective recycling.
You can't sell it for money.
There is also a trash can here
. It
seems that it is full of paper.
This should be It's not
what kind of
fruit is this.
It's such a big bag of fruit.
It's a bit hard
to look at the bag below. Is it
this bag? It's not
this bag. It's also
this bag. It's not this bag. It's in a plastic shell.
Look at
this bag. It's some fruits and vegetables
. It’s not particularly good.
Many of them are crushed
, but when you pick them,
this one is broken.
This one is okay
, but you can pick some good ones
. There are quite a lot of bananas
, and there are also
quite a few bananas,
which are extremely difficult to sell in supermarkets.
Pick some that can be used.
I think the tomatoes I took away
were all stems.
You could pull the tomatoes and they would fall off. Look at the picked
tomatoes. Although they don’t look very good
, they are completely edible.
Today’s harvest is not bad. There are
two big bags of bread
and some fruits and vegetables.
Now let's go to Switzerland immediately
to see how my old friend Alfie
makes garbage look like it can't be eaten.
Let's go
. Now we have arrived in Lausanne, Switzerland,
where our first protagonist today is studying at
the Hotel Lausanne. School of Management
coucou Yooupi You are here.
Your hotel management school, ranked number one in the world,
is different.
The places you see now
are the lobby of the school.
All your students have classes here?
It’s upstairs, but there is a reception here. The local
kitchen
is not only a kitchen
, it is also a place where we usually have a dish creation class.
There will be teachers and students who can operate
and various instruments for researching dishes.
This is a place where I once led a team to win
the cooking championship of the whole school. Yes
, as a chef
and a Chinese,
yes ,
this is your canteen.
Yes, this is a part of the canteen.
It is so high-end.
This is my mentor Michel De Matteis.
He is the best craftsman in France.
Why do they all wear suits? Are they teachers
? This is a mandatory clothing requirement for
students .
If you don't wear
the same clothes as in China, the dean will catch you and make you stand.
So I think
you are an outsider and it shouldn't count
. Now that I have arrived at Alfie's house,
I am going to give you one. A small test.
This is the garbage I picked up yesterday
, but the pear is not in good condition.
Basic ingredients such as tomatoes,
potatoes and eggs can be used
, but I am still confident
to turn it into a Michelin-level delicacy
. Let's wait and see
. Today I'm going to make a five-course meal for Yooupi.
First, an appetizer,
a soup, then a meat,
then a seafood
, and finally a dessert.
This bread has been expired for about a week.
It feels a little evaporated and dry
, but it's still edible. No problem,
I found. This radish is very popular in French food.
Normally
, you only need the two slices in the middle.
The rest
can be used as a salad for the staff.
In the restaurant
today, will you make more traditional French food?
I will integrate myself.
For example, French food likes to add some Asian elements to many things now
. You use Sichuan peppercorns to make Western food.
For Hanyuan Gongjiao, do a Sichuan-French fusion.
This is a low-temperature slow-cooked chicken
. I will set a low temperature
and it will maintain a low temperature. Constant temperature
, isn't that just a heating rod?
Yes
,
the eggs are sieved, right?
This fish has been expired for a while,
but it is smoked and then salted.
I think there should be no problem.
Add the marinated seafood
and then a little Sugar to make it fresh
and then a little salt, right?
After dinner,
we used these fruits and vegetables to make
Provence Fruit and Vegetable Smoked Fish with Garlic Mayonnaise.
Oh my gosh, this dish is so beautiful.
I don’t even know how to put my fork in it.
It ’s so delicious .
Our Northeastern pickles are a bit similar
In fact, these two dishes are similar
but the details are different.
We used these ingredients to make
a cold onion-flavored tomato soup with tomato preserves.
Your dish and plate are so beautiful.
Try the taste.
This tomato is lavender. There is basil oil in
the dried syrup,
which can bring out some more complex flavors.
It is not as simple as a roasted small tomato.
We used this bunch of fruits and vegetables to make
seafood avocado tartar with basil cream sauce
, which is French style. It's a very classic combination of
seafood, avocado and a sauce.
It looks very summery to me.
It's a lot of green and it feels
delicious.
Don't look at this thing. It's made from rubbish
. It's made like this by Alfie. It's
really fragrant.
We use this. Helinqi’s chicken legs
were mixed with home-made seasonings to make
pan-fried chicken legs with soy sauce and Sichuan pepper foam.
I’ll help you cut this chicken.
I’m telling you, this chicken
smells like Sichuan. That Sichuan peppercorn.
Oh my God,
this Sichuan peppercorn is sent from China by my mother. I
also used it to stir
- fry the hot pot base.
In fact, I’m quite curious.
If you were to intern at a Michelin restaurant,
would there be waste in a restaurant like this?
There is more or less waste
, but in the past two years in Europe I’m becoming more and more aware of this problem.
If you can’t eat anything, treat it as fertilizer
. If you can eat it, distribute it to employees.
I think this is actually good. It’s
equivalent to maximizing the use of ingredients.
We
used these pears to make
French red wine. Stewed Pear and Tremella Rock Sugar Snow Pear
is a dessert that completely combines Chinese and Western styles.
This is actually one of my masterpieces.
Normally, I also make it for some of my foreign friends,
and they all like it very much.
You can also make some wolfberry,
longan, etc.
Actually, you can tell. You really love cooking.
Have you ever thought about opening a restaurant
of your own in the future ?
I haven't graduated yet
, but as you know, I have prepared some projects.
In the future, I would rather integrate some cultures
and create my own style. For some works and things,
I can only say good luck to you.
After you open a restaurant in the future,
it should be free for me to eat in your restaurant.
If you don’t use the air force, I’ll give you the fish you caught in the sea. In other
words, it’s the same as not saying it
, but it’s not wrong. Knowing that I am in the air force every day,
today I challenge Michelin with rubbish.
I think it is quite successful . I
still want to thank my old friend Alfie
. If you like this video,
don’t forget to like and follow.
Then we will see you
next Saturday.